<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Reverse-Engineering on deadc0de</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/reverse-engineering/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Reverse-Engineering on deadc0de</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.147.8</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/reverse-engineering/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Complete Technical Analysis: Reverse Engineering the Logitech F710 Wireless Gamepad and Developing a Security PoC</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/joystick-f710/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/joystick-f710/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;executive-summary&#34;&gt;Executive Summary&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This comprehensive technical analysis documents the complete reverse engineering of the Logitech F710 wireless gamepad, including the development of a proof-of-concept (PoC) that demonstrates critical security vulnerabilities in the device&amp;rsquo;s wireless protocol. Our research revealed that the F710 uses an unencrypted, unauthenticated 2.4GHz proprietary protocol vulnerable to replay attacks, signal injection, and device spoofing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Key findings:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;No encryption&lt;/strong&gt; on the wireless protocol&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;No mutual authentication&lt;/strong&gt; between controller and dongle&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Vulnerable to replay attacks&lt;/strong&gt; with basic SDR equipment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Successfully developed PoC&lt;/strong&gt; for controller spoofing and input injection&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Legacy protocol&lt;/strong&gt; similar to vulnerable Logitech Unifying receivers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Logitech F710 represents a significant portion of the wireless gamepad market, particularly in industrial and commercial applications where its reliability and compatibility are valued. However, our research reveals that this popularity comes with serious security implications.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
